pigtagram.com 2019-07-18

# Privacy Policy - Pigtagram

Pigtagram LLC operates the website name Pigtagram.club which provides the social media online services.

This "Privacy Policy" page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our service, the website Name Pigtagram.club

If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The Personal Information that we collect are used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at Website Pigtagram.com, unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.

### Information Collection and Use

For a better user experience while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your social media usernames. The information that we collect will be used to provide you a better user experience, contact or identify you.

### Like Data

Like many web sites we collect information that your browser sends when you visit our Site. We would like to inform you that whenever you visit our website, we collect information that your browser sends to us that is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser version, pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.

### Cookies

Cookies are small sized files with a piece of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.

Our website uses these "cookies" to collect information to improve our website user experience. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our web site's functions.

### Service Providers

We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:

To facilitate our Service; To provide the Service on our behalf; To perform Service-related services; or To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. We want to inform our Service users that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.

### Security

We care your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Links to Other Sites

Our website may have links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, website or in a related subject do not hesitate to contact us from contact page.
